Rebels called the rebels for consist of some pre-built binaries.
It includes some tools, like a sealed Android emulator, Basle, etc. Under the previous folder, we
can find some prebuilt tools like assembled Android emulator.
So this is a standard emulator which you can download from Android website, or it comes as part of
the Android Studio or ingilizce.
So here you can find the data in version and the like to and then assume a suit contains this a region.
So this is the one which we have, which we will use for building a particular project and opening that
project in an idea suggests Android Studio or in the lead later in this course.
And then there is a tool called 8As.
So this is a tool for testing, basically, and that is something for a cloud and then the basal, and
there are many other tools.
These are all pre-built tools, which is also shipped with a wispy SDK folder.
SDK folder consists of many SDK tools sources.
It also contains some instructions to build the SDK for a specific Build SDK folder.
You can find the sources of many SDK tools like Epic Game Builder and it is the emulator and Fine Java
here.
Any statistical launcher the steam folder The System folder contains lower level file system libraries,
applications and components.
This is the embedded Linux folder.
Here you can find folders for a Kleenex logging lib.
It's ideal and many low level configurations under the system folder.
You can find a lot of embedded Linux configurations, basically.
For example, if you are changing some AC policies, we learn about SC policies in a later session.
But in case if you want to change SC policies, then you will be changing this private public folders.
And there are many low level configurations in this folder, so this can be considered as the folder
for embedded Linux.
Then you have the test folder.
It does.
The folder contains that best suits like suits cat box witness render to suit emptiest, the main line
to suit, etc...
So under test, you can find all these up folders, which consist of the card books wittiest and a pursuit
empty and insidious root.
Then comes the two return folder.
The torture folder contains files related to benchmark and BGA profiles, so ToolChain Folder consist
of a couple of south folders for benchmarking and B.G. profiles.
And finally, we have the Tools folder.
The Doors folder again consists of some tools like a Assign a seal, trade filtration, etc. We have
the tools folder here, though it has many other tools for it.
Biggest sign a cloud API.
Find a recent resource generation.